(Music) Open your heart to the incredible gifts that civilization gives to us. You flip a switch, and there is electric light. You turn a faucet, and there is warm water and cold water, and drinkable water. It's a gift that millions and millions in the world will never experience. So these are just a few of an enormous number of gifts to which we can open your heart. And so I wish you that you will open your heart to all these blessings, and let them flow through you, that everyone whom you will meet on this day will be blessed by you, just by your eyes, by your smile, by your touch, just by your presence. Let the gratefulness overflow into blessing all around you. (Music) And then, it will really be a good day. (Applause) Louie Schwartzberg: Thank you. Thank you very much. (Applause)
(Música) Abran sus corazones a los increíbles regalos de la civilización. Si accionan un interruptor, hay luz eléctrica. Si abren el grifo, hay agua fría y tibia y potable. Es un regalo que millones y millones jamás experimentarán en el mundo. Estos son solo algunos de los muchos regalos a los cuales podemos abrir nuestros corazones. Por lo tanto, deseo que abran sus corazones a todas estas bendiciones, y que las dejen fluir a través de Uds., para hoy que bendigan a todos aquellos que conozcan, simplemente con sus ojos, con su sonrisa, con su roce, o con su simple presencia. Dejen que la gratitud se transforme en bendición a su alrededor, y entonces será realmente un buen día. (Música) (Aplausos) Louie Schwartzberg: Gracias. Muchísimas gracias. (Aplausos)